人类征服了另一颗行星的天空
We have opened the skies of of another planet.
机智号火星直升机是人类首个外星有动力航空器
机智号为人类打开了火星空中探索的大门
Ingenuity really opened the door for aerial exploration on Mars.
这个小巧又勇敢的直升机超出了所有人的预期
It's just been this plucky little helicopter that just defied everybody's expectations.
近三年内 72次飞行
机智号于2024年1月18日完成了它最后一次飞行
我为机智号为人类带来的一切感到无比自豪与感激
I'm incredibly proud and grateful for all that Ingenuity has been able to give us.
最后你想对机智号说些什么吗?
What would you say to Ingenuity directly one last time?
天啊 我有点泪目了……
Oh, you're gonna make me cry, you know-
我会对机智号说什么?
What would I say to Ingenuity?
跟你说再见 真的很艰难
It's really hard to say goodbye to you.
我想说 谢谢你
I would say, thank you.
机智号 感谢你让我们相聚于此
Ingenuity, thank you for bringing us all together.
感谢你带领人类在火星的天空中探险 我们永远不会忘记你
Thank you for leading the charge in our adventure on Mars and we will never forget you.
晚安
Rest well.
谢谢你 机智号
Thank you Ingenuity.
Thanks Ingenuity.
谢谢你 机智号